

## @

z.h.juma@hotmail.com



971552391939



Dubai, United Arab Emirates



02 June 1995

## **EDUCATION**

High School - Scientific - 76% Al Raya High School, Dubai, United Arab Emirates, June 2013

Foundation **UAE University**, Al Ain, United Arab Emirates, June 2014

IELTS – **British Council** Band 5.5 2020-2022

UG Bachelor of Business & Quality Management **Hamdan Bin Mohammed Smart University,** Dubai, United Arab Emirates, September 2020

# **ZUBAIDA HABIB JUMA**

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a talented ambitus and hardworking individual furthermore; I am adept at handling multi tasks on a daily basis competently and at working well under pressure. I have organized the work function for the last 6 years with great success. Recently, I am going to complete my Bachelor Degree in Business and Quality Management.

#### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

Ms Word, Excel, Access and power point

Mac-Window user

## TRAINING ATTENDED

First Aid Certificate (ISSUED by HABC).

Emergency responder training.

Station Master & Station Agent training.

Information & Security Controller training.

Lift rescue.

Fire extinguisher training.

## **WORK HISTORY**

January 2020 - June 2022

**Dubai Metro - Station Manager**, Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- Organize emergency evacuation procedures during emergency situation.
- Ensuring that the station facilities in a safe and good working condition.
- Attending and handling passenger's complaints in the station.
- Dealing with I'll passengers and report to Operation Control Centre and request for ambulance or provide first aid if needed.

- Dealing with contractors and visitors in the station and give access.
- Report to Police in case if there is any crime or anti-social behaviors.

#### January 2018 - January 2020

## **Dubai Tram - Information and Security Controller**, Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- Monitored, authorized and recorded entrance and departure of vehicles and visitors.
- Secured doors and gates across office buildings and grounds, maintaining optimal security standards.
- Delivered emergency procedures and liaised with police, firefighters, and medical staff.
- Updated team and coordinated responsibilities using two-way radio system.
- Access the CCTV and telecommunications recording systems for investigation purposes.
- Direct Customer Service Agent to respond and deal with incidents and events that happens in Dubai Tram Stations.

#### January 2016 - December 2017

## **Dubai Metro - Station Manager**, Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- Maintained clean, safe working environments to eliminate accident risks.
- Led and managed administrative staff to maintain smooth daily operations.
- Conducting briefing to the Station Agent, and indoctrinating then with the policy and procedure the commencement of the day.
- Monitoring, controlling and reviewing CCTV cameras.
- Customer service.

## **LANGUAGE**

Arabic & English